spinglo.com 2012-07-05

# Spinglo privacy - Pages - Spinglo

## Privacy policy

As Spinglo is a community that is all about trust we feel it is important to share our privacy policy with you. If you have any questions about this policy we can be reached by email at [privacy@spinglo.com](mailto:privacy@spinglo.com).

###  Information We Collect

When you become a member of Spinglo we will collect some personal information from you such as: name, email address, etc.

### How We Collect

Some of the information we receive is through the registration process. When you agree to become an Spinglo member we ask you to provide this personal information. Additionally, we use cookies and other technologies to recognize you and uniquely identify your browser. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. We also automatically receive such information as IP address, your type of browser and ISP.

### Why We Collect

This information allows us to customize your experience and the advertisements you see, to store your preferences and record session information. The information we collect is used for internal review to improve the content of our Website, to conduct research and analysis to help improve your experience, to ensure the technical functionality of our network, and to create and develop new ideas and services for our members.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. From time to time, we may use personal information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. In such event, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. We reserve the right to revise or update this policy at any time.

We may disclose and use personally identifiable and other information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our terms and conditions, policies and agreements, to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, and to protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Spinglo. We may also disclose and use personally identifiable and other information when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so.
